thejokeyard.com 2017-08-13

# Privacy Policy

### Collection and Use of Information

Your data is used for purposes that you expect it to be used for such as customising content to your preferences or providing services you requested. This may include providing you personalized content, features to enable you to interact with others, securing your data, and communicating about, improving, or troubleshooting the products or services being provided.

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

### Disclosure to Third Parties

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

We may also disclose your personal information 

  * as required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if thejokeyard.com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

### Tracking Technologies

#### Cookies

We may use cookies to keep track of your preferences, profile and login information. Cookies are also used to collect general usage and volume statistical information that does not include personal information.

#### Web beacons

Our Web pages contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) and are used along with cookies to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of our customer communications and marketing campaigns. Our Web pages may also contain electronic images known as Web beacons (sometimes called single-pixel gifs) that are set by our third party partners. Web beacons are used along with cookies enabling our partners to compile aggregated statistics to analyze how our site is used.

#### Links to Other Web Sites

Our site may provide links to other web sites whose privacy policies may be different from our own. Any information you submit to these sites will be governed by the their privacy policies. We recommend that you read the privicy policy of all websites you visit.

#### Ad Serving

Like most websites, we allow third party ad networks to serve advertisements. Ads served may include tracking technologies which collect aggregate information about your behavior on this and other sites.

Ads may be selected for you based on information gathered by these third party ad networks.

#### Opt Out Of Third Party Ad Tracking

All modern web browsers provide the ability for you to opt out of third party cookies such as those used by ad networks. This can be achieved by making a few small changes to your browsers setting.

Due to the large number of browsers and browser versions available, it is not possible for us to provide detailed directions on how to disable third party tracking in your browser. Instead we recommend you visit the [About Cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=1) website which provides more detailed information.

You can also visit [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to learn more about behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising.

#### Google Ad Serving

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
